healthynewage.com 2017-05-01

# Privacy Policy, FTC Disclosure Statement, and Legal Disclaimer – Healthynewage.com

## Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site. 

We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices, and our customer’s needs. 

What information do we collect? When you visit this web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our web site. 

**1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

Registration Information – When you register for any of our products, services, or newsletters you will provide us information about yourself. 

Email Information – If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone. 

**2\. Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial web sites, our web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?” and web server log files to collect information about how our web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our web site, and the web sites visited just before and just after our web site. 

_How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?_

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing the products and services you requested, to process your payment, to monitor the use of the service, our marketing and promotional efforts and improve our content and service offerings, and customize our site’s content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personally identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law. 

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our web site, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at the link provided on the newsletter. 

_What Are Cookies?_

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses. 

_How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?_

As you visit and browse our web site, the site uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our web site and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies. 

_IP Addresses_

Your computer uses IP addresses every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. 

_Sharing and Selling Information_

We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested. 

_How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?_

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us at the usual address. 

_What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?_

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. We may also disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the Public. 

_What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?_

We are not responsible for the practices employed by web sites linked to or from our web site or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our web site. 

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our web site to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on our web site, is subject to that web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

_Your Consent_

By using our web site, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice. 

_Our Commitment To Data Security_

Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your Country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

_Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out_

This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing, we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible. 

_Surveys & Contests_

From time-to-time, our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

_A Special Note About Children_

Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 14) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians. 

_Acquisition or Changes in Ownership_

In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred. 

_Policy Modifications_

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent. 

## FTC Disclosure Statement

HealthyNewAge.com intends to be fully compliant with Federal Trade Commission (FTC) policies regarding marketing and advertising. 

All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network. Those advertisements will always be identified as paid advertisements. For example, we have a material connection with Google and are paid a commission when a visitor clicks through on advertising elements marked as “Google” on our web site. In addition, some of the links to products and services on this web site generate affiliate commissions. If you have a question about whether we have a material connection with any product or service upon which we write, please contact us. 

The compensation received will never influence the content published on this web site. Even though we receive compensation from advertising and affiliate programs, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences. The views and opinions expressed on this web site are purely the writer’s own and do not necessarily represent those of HealthyNewAge.com. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider, or party in question. 

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest. 

## Legal Disclaimer

_Medical Information Disclaimer_

The information on this web site is provided for educational and entertainment purposes only, and is in no way intended to diagnose, cure, or treat any medical or other condition. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health provider prior to starting any new diet and ask your doctor any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. In addition to all other limitations and disclaimers in this agreement, service provider and its third party providers disclaim any liability or loss in connection with the content provided on this web site. 

_Disclaimer of Warranty and Limitation of Liability_

Owner makes no representations, warranties, or assurances as to the accuracy, currency, or completeness of the products, services, and content provided via this web site. All statements have been used in good faith and the necessary actions have been taken to verify such statements with the appropriate parties. 

Owner provides its products, services, and content “as is” and expressly disclaims warranties of any kind, either expressed or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement. The entire risk as to the quality and performance of the products, services, and content is with you. Should the products, services, and content prove defective, you assume the cost of all necessary servicing, repair, correction, or replacement. 

Owner reserves the right to make changes to its products, services, and content in this web site, or may make improvements and/or changes in the products, services, and content and other materials described in this site, at any time without notice or to the products, services, and content described therein without notice. 

Without limiting the foregoing, Owner shall not be liable to you or your business for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, special, or punitive damages or lost or imputed profits or royalties arising out of the use of or inability to use this web site or any products, services, and content provided (including but not limited to injury, death, loss of data, or data being rendered inaccurate or losses sustained by you or third parties or a failure of the products, services, and content to operate with any other programs, whether for breach of warranty or any obligation arising there from or otherwise, whether liability is asserted in contract or tort (including negligence and strict product liability) and irrespective of whether Owner have been advised of the possibility of any such loss or damage.
